It's my life. It's your life.
Fighting for tomorrow.
Go get what you really want.
I want more. Any one more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life. It's your life.
Run like a winter fire.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going.
I'll not stay.
Let's do it again, you
know what I mean, baby.
No one can make it my dream come true.
Don't you feel it, I
really don't know what is.
Something is testing me every day.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
I know I never wanna come back here.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
The great end of the unknown rules.
Standing up, blowing up.
My dream is getting wilder.
I'm not afraid, beat me, hit me.
I will never turn around.
Another day, another chance.
You know it's never too late.
If I can do it, so can you.
It's my life, it's your life.
Fight if you can't
achieve
your
goal.
Let's keep on going, roaring.
It's my life, it's your life.
Fighting for your eyes that
I want, but you really want.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the gate.
It's my life, it's your life,
shine like a star to be good.
I know you're strong, just that
you can't achieve your best.
Let's keep on going, I love this.
You make my day every day.
Now, little people, are
you guys ready to wreck?
This factory made you
don't tell to suffer.
It's time to collect your payback.
Bust it.
AHHHHH!
Good luck, little bros.
The rest of this is in your hands, Luffy.
Send the rescue team over here!
There's injured people! Sir!
Showtime!
Mwah!
Half moon flavor!
Kiddos!
I thought you had it up
to here with me before.
What happened to all the big talk, huh?
Did you really think I
was just a gifted matador
whose name sends ripples
through the stadium?
You may have been the strongest
competitor at one point,
but that wasn't meant to last forever.
I astound all while
slaying the competition.
The current hero of the Coliseum
is the brilliant Diamante!
Did you really think I
was just a gifted matador?
The title means nothing to me!
Fame can be evasive, I know!
Be careful.
A fine attempt.
You almost had me.
I can't blame you.
You have been running
around the kingdom all day.
Then you gotta protect your daughter
and the ground's all wobbly.
Life's crazy.
I'm afraid you're a day late
and a leg short, my man.
Anyone would be at the limit by now.
Only a fool would patronize me for my leg.
Really?
If I were to use that as an excuse,
I would then have come here.
I take great pride.
It was a small sacrifice
for the man who saved me.
If you say so, I won't feel guilty
about attacking your weak spot.
But it won't be any fun for me to utterly
crush you while you
need your nappy whappy.
So what do you say?
How about we pass the
time with the game, huh?
And now, the last showtime!
It's confetti.
It's just paper?
Confetti? Yes!
paper, no, I wonder what
the mystery item could be,
and now for my next
trick, ripple, release.
spiky metal balls—look at
the breathtaking sights!
It's like falling stardust, Robin!
We have no place to hide,
Robiland—protect Rebecca!
You're in danger too, commander!
Do not waste concern on me!
What a great view the last one you'll see?
I hate to boast, but my stardust
can wipe out an entire army,
and it's nearly impossible to survive!
to survive Luckily, we are in this field.
Meal fluid!
Forgive me, flowers.
It's too bad you're not under here.
Adios, pal!
Death and hungry!
Blower Umbrella!
That was a close one.
Oh, not too shabby.
Pay attention.
Kittles, wow!
Any army that would fall through
this trickery surely lacks training.
This is insanity!
How are you smacking my
stardust away mid-air?
Can you also walk through
rain without getting wet?
Fine, then.
Mother, no!
The sky's falling, kiddos.
I bet you wouldn't have stumbled if you
still had that extra leg right about now.
You can't do this to him! Diamante!
Stop it, Rebecca!
Please stay under the canopy!
Father, no!
You bastard!
I will never forgive
you for this, Diamante!
Fine, then don't forgive me!
Come make me pay!
You want a piece?
I got a bullet for you!
Just like your mommy!
Please unhand me, Robin!
I have to kill this man!
I'm not sure how much more the
Flower Umbrella can withstand.
Damn you! No way!
Lower your weapon right now!
Now, Rebecca, this is my fight.
Ten years, you have suffered
on your own. Come here.
You need to recover.
You'll die.
For ten years, you've
upheld your mother's wish.
My mother told me I should never
hurt others, no matter what.
But you must protect yourself
from those who would hurt you.
Rebecca has never once wounded anybody!
So far, she's won every buck just by
letting her foes fall off the side!
You only win by disqualification!
Chance of blood, you weakling!
You're a huge coward! Boo!
You should be ashamed of your victory.
There's no way a gladiator
should claim glory.
I hope you get stabbed this time!
You're a descendant of evil!
You're nothing but garbage!
though you fought in the coliseum
you still haven't harmed a soul
your hands are still clean they're
untainted your mother's heart
reside in those pristine hands
mother
so i will not allow for you to
stain them with this lousy's blood
from now on you will
live your life peacefully
What the hell?
How are you standing?
Are you solid steel?
Come on.
You're crazy.
No, I take that back.
This pain.
Is proof that I am human.
You wouldn't understand, you monster!
This is nothing compared to
the grief of being forgotten.
Skirtlet.
Damn it, why did you wait for me?
Why are you here?
I see now.
It seems I've been erased
from everyone's memories.
Our promises.
Our time together.
Gone.
My daughter is hungry.
And she's waiting for me.
I'm your husband.
I beg you.
These useless tin arms of mine.
I can't even feel your
warmth one last time!
You'll never be able
to grasp the unbearable
ache of being unable to
feel anything you touch!
Compared to all the despicable acts you
committed against the people of Dressrosa,
what I suffer now is scarcely pain at all
if I'm sure that
anything and I am this
kingdom solid rage
manifested here to collect
pay back
you
were in
your prime two decades?
You should have peaked by now!
Don't overlook my sword skills!
You fool!
You ready to call the curtains yet?
I'll show you to your grave!
Whoa!
Looks like my metal rain cleared up.
I suppose it's more fitting
if I finish you off myself.
Just like I did with Scarlet, and
I bet you miss her, don't you?
So cruel he keeps taunting them,
laughing about scarlet's death,
like rubbing salt in a wound.
I'm sorry, king Rick;
our searches ended in vain—a man
named diamante got ahead of our party.
party
Scarlet was found in the town,
but she was killed by gunshot.
You killed Scarlet?
Oh, yeah?
That was your older sister, huh?
It's such a shame she had to go
and buy food at the market today.
If she could have controlled her
hunger, she wouldn't have been killed.
What a greedy sow.
Jake, let go of me!
Please don't act in haste.
You must think rationally!
Just let me go!
Help me out!
We must stay in the palace!
It's for your own protection!
You don't know how this ends!
My next strike is strong
enough to shatter the earth!
Take this!
This!
Think that wounded leg can dodge
what I am about to throw at you?
I will not dodge.
A thing!
If you're not gonna avoid my attack,
then you're just a damn fool!
Now I'm taking our peace back!
Half moon.
Treno.
Shit.
You have my gratitude, Robiland.
Father!
Father, you need to get patched up.
I could not save your mother's life,
but I'll devote mine to protect
yours, whatever the cost.
Someday, happiness will return to
you, Until then, I'll stay right here.
He defeated Diamante!
Crazy.
He took down someone.
So strong.
But how is Kiros, though?
Does he still live?
He lives.
Kiros is injured, but safe.
And Rebecca, too.
It's thanks to Nico
Robin that she survived.
It's unbelievable that he took out
the top Don Quixote executives!
And the Coliseum Hero at that!
Is that a joke?
You must have forgotten that Kiros
was the original undefeated champion!
We truly thought the Don
Quixote family was invincible,
but here they are dropping
one after another!
He did well that's our commander
Now the tables are turning
in our favor at last
The warriors recruited by
this Straw Hat pirates have
taken down the lower-ranking
executives one after another
There's only four major players
of the Don Quixote family left
Bellamy the hyena, then two high-ranking
executives, Pika, and Treble.
After that, only the current king and
warlord of the sea, Doflamingo, remains.
That's it.
Our final hurdle!
I never thought they'd get this far.
These Straw Hat people are amazing!
I can't believe we tried
to kill these magnificent
bastards in an attempt to save ourselves!
Well, there's no use crying
over spilt milk, right?
Plus, you guys are saying
such nice stuff about us now.
I can't stay mad at you.
Old King Rick, where are
you going, Your Highness?
I do not believe my life
is threatened any longer.
I'm going to town.
There is still much left to be done.
Allow me to escort you, sir.
I have very little faith in
the government or the Navy.
Everyone's feeling helpless right now.
They think there's no escaping
the sick game or the birdcage.
I say we all go.
Let's spread a message of
hope throughout the kingdom.
It seems we have finally captured
what one would call a breather.
Hey, where did that one
Navy admiral guy go anyway?
Did you not take note, Sir Usopp?
That decorated fellow traveled
into town a while ago.
In that case, gather up all the
civilians you can to one place.
Make certain it's secure.
We will keep them all safe. Sir!
The hell?
That bastard.
Hey, father.
What's that shaking?
Rebecca!
No!
I thought Zoro had him.
That's Pika.
Killer?
Oh, Diamante!
That's a real bad look for a
top executive in our family!
Father!
As foreseen, I did not come here
for a mere one-on-one skirmish.
As long as an enemy
stands, the fight persists.
You can barely move.
Please don't do this.
Fall back, Rebecca.
Quick question.
Why is old King Rick worth
a squat to you people?
Rebecca, isn't he the reason
why everybody hates you so much?
Why do you respect that puke?
That's nonsense.
You despicable people framed him.
My father-in-law is my personal savior.
He showed benevolence
to this young ruffian.
The Rick bloodline upheld
a reputation for being
a family that understood
the value of peace.
Our richness came from
routine joys, clear skies,
thriving blossoms, a
kingdom of gentle hearts.
That's the backbone on
which we flourished.
Our entire nation wishes for your wicked
family's swift removal
so he may reign again.
I see!
Huh?
He left.
The hell?
That scared the crap out of me!
Pika escaped to the third level.
What a pain in the ass.
He's supposed to fight me.
Why is he in such a hurry?
How am I supposed to
knock the snot out of him
when he's scurrying
around like a damn mole?
As soon as I close in on him, he's done.
Just go!
Lord Pika, please have mercy on us!
You forget we're on your team!
Hunting the injured, spineless prick!
You've betrayed the family, BB-5!
Steal me!
Watch out!
Trilestone!
That big, shrill bastard!
You're pissing me off!
Cut the crap already!
Stop going after all the wounded people!
I'm over here!
Light stone!
One sword style.
Demon horse!
You know, Roranora Zoro,
there's a very important someone
up on the King's Black Zone!
The King of Dressrosa? Thorma!
Get to the point, soprano man!
Aside from the has-been king
and some of his followers,
I heard the samurai and god Usuf are
on the king's plateau right now, too.
So, if I understand correctly,
suddenly the whole kingdom wants to
put King Rick back on the throne.
Yeah, what's it to you?
It pisses me off his what?
Dolphy's the only one worthy here.
What the hell?
Son of a...
Where's that big behemoth headed now?
What is he gonna do?
Dressrosa belongs to
the Don Quixote family!
He's gonna walk! Let's go!
The statue is moving! Run!
Oh, jeez. Are you kidding me?
Godless bastard!
He's trying to kill the king.
Damn it.
That's why he ditched me
all the way back here.
I can't catch up.
I played right into his hands.
Got to think fast of what to do.
One quick punch from him and it
could take out the entire plateau.
If I don't think of some
way to shut him down,
Usopp and that king guy will
be crushed in an instant.
Pirate Hunter, we won't let you
get any closer to Lord Pika.
I don't have time for that crap.
Zoro!
He's controlling the statue.
And headed for the King's Plateau.
Grandfather. Who's up?
Whoa!
Hey, man, screw you!
Plan one.
Long distance slash.
Now I'd have to travel too
far and it'd barely nick him.
Plan two.
Jump up and get on top.
Impossible.
Plan three.
Shout out warning Usopp and the others.
Usopp!
No chance in hell.
Not with all the noise.
Plan four.
Call him by transponder snail
and tell him hurry up and run.
Oh, must have dropped it.
Don't come any closer!
Even if I do manage to
get the message out,
there's not enough time for him to react.
Smash it for good!
Give him hell!
He has his sights on King Rick.
It's not our fight, but this
isn't sitting well with me.
Stop right there!
Don't do it, Snow Monster!
The legendary sniper king
is on that very plateau.
You, rock boy, you want to fight?
Then I volunteer my. I
see
now the pirate hunter
was a few steps ahead of us?
Glad I saved my King Punch as he advised.
I've got your back, Rick, my friend.
Hey, King Punch guy!
Excuse me?
I'm Elisabello, the King of Prodents.
I'd watch your tongue if I were you.
I told you, trying to
shatter him won't work.
You gotta hit his flesh and blood
or else he'll keep coming back.
What are you suggesting then?
I'll do anything, just save me!
Pirate hunter?
Well, give me two minutes.
King Rick, you there?
Plan five.
Fly him to the sky and chop him up.
Yep, that's the one.
This looks dire.
Grandfather's up there. Mr.
Sniper King!
Just run away!
Hey pirate hunter, don't
make me wait too long, yo!
Two by four, if you mean
Commodore—that's me!
Yeah, whatever you're the guy
that threw that other guy?
guy like a cannonball, right?
Get smashed like a bug, Rick!
Open fire!
It is I you want. Face me.
Do not put my people through
any more needless havoc.
Everybody, it's time to flee!
You must get off the plateau!
Everyone has exited.
It's your turn now.
Father, hurry up!
Viola and Tank, lead everyone to safety.
He's only after me. Just go.
You don't have to do this.
King Rick, come with us.
I can't.
This may be the only opportunity.
I am at peace with my choice.
Now go, Tank.
How sweet!
Well, if that's what you
really want, I won't complain!
What the hell?
Pirate Hunter or Lumbus?
What are you two plotting?
You're certain you wish to do this?
This technique is not meant
for throwing someone safely.
Come on, carnivore.
Just throw me.
That bastard is only going after those
who won't fight back. You ready? Yeah.
Rick, you're no king.
You're not gonna have to lead anyone!
Kumadori!
If you won't run, neither will we.
We stand with King Rick!
Aw, Rick!
Did your sheep forgive you for
that decade-long misunderstanding?
How's a pacifist like you
gonna protect your kingdom?
You couldn't even save
your own reputation, Rick.
A kingdom's strength lies
in its military might.
You know nothing about true authority.
I'll crush you.
I'll crush it all.
ZEI!
KING Rick!
The town is going to pulverize me!
KILLER!
BOLING!
What you say is true.
I fail to protect my kingdom.
I will never sit upon that throne again.
However.
To the bitter end.
I will remain true.
Nine mountains and eight
seas make one world.
One thousand worlds make one Chilliocosm.
One Chilliocosm to the power of three.
And there's nothing I can't cut.
Three-sword style secret technique.
Are you naive or what?
If the only means for me to survive
is becoming a cold-blooded killer,
then I fearlessly choose death.
There is no future for
a nation of slaughter.
King Rick, we all
proudly stand behind you!
Why do you think so many
do-gooders are lost to history?
They always die off for
leaving a mark on the world!
The billion-fold world
to kill your cousin!
Good, he's in the top half.
Rory Noah!
Go, Zoro!
Dead stones.
Moving stones,
it seems like his real body is shifting
to one of the newly sliced pieces.
And every time I split him,
the other side dies off.
As long as he's up here, he
can't burrow in the ground.
Come on out! Peek up!
How long are you going
to keep hiding from me?
Soap by cornering me.
You must think you've won.
You've got it all figured out.
Just cut some stones
and you can defeat me.
Well, good luck cutting
through my Haki, you moron!
A Haki user?
Once I pound you into the
ground, it's all over for you!
I don't have any more time to
waste on a pebble like you!
Take that back!
Nine mountains and eight seas.
There's nothing I can't cut.
Right in hell!
Uranoa, Zoro!
Three thousand worlds!
Now quit picking on the innocent, will ya?
What an upstanding guy!
Zoro!
He really did it, it's over!
He saved my friend, Rick!
Oh crap!
His remains are still falling!
We're all gonna die!
Rescue me! Zoro!
That's your cue!
All right!
King Kong!
How dare you tricking me into using
the king punch for custodial labor!
You'll regret this,
you disrespectful punk!
That settles that?